<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>random_jy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on random_jy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <copyright>Jon Young</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 19:57:16 EST</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Resolutions for 2015</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/resolutions-for-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 19:57:16 EST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/resolutions-for-2015/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Now that it is February, time to make some goals for myself in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;be-an-even-awesomer-husband-father:87223ae63adbc1cf20a73dc9414eb665&#34;&gt;Be an even awesomer Husband &amp;amp; Father&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to think I&amp;rsquo;m doing a pretty decent job at this already, but there&amp;rsquo;s always room for improvement. And our family will be expanding from 3 to 4 in 2015!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;make-a-blog-and-keep-writing-for-it:87223ae63adbc1cf20a73dc9414eb665&#34;&gt;Make a blog&amp;hellip; and keep writing for it&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, you&amp;rsquo;re here, so I&amp;rsquo;m doing pretty well so far. Of course, we&amp;rsquo;ll see if I can keep going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve written what I&amp;rsquo;ve got so far using &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty sweet static site generator written in &lt;a href=&#34;http://golang.org/&#34;&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt;. I like that I can write everything in markdown. After using github for a couple of years, I have problems writing in anything other than Markdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;read-2-books-a-month:87223ae63adbc1cf20a73dc9414eb665&#34;&gt;Read 2 Books a Month&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year I averaged maybe 1 book a month. I read mostly fiction in 2014. In 2015 I&amp;rsquo;m looking to read both fiction and non-fiction. Ideally one of each type every month. Not sure how the other goals will affect this one. I plan to make time to read in the mornings, after I wake up. Hopefully the house will still be quiet at that point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;re-implement-this-blog:87223ae63adbc1cf20a73dc9414eb665&#34;&gt;Re-Implement this blog&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is definitely a stretch goal, but I&amp;rsquo;d like to try re-implementing this blog using various frameworks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rails (no experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;django (some experience from work stuff)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;elixir (no experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;go &amp;amp; its magnificent stdlib (some experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideally, I&amp;rsquo;ll write the blog apps to intake the same markdown used by Hugo. And then take advantage of various CI/CD pipelines to deploy new posts too all the apps at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the log term plan becomes use DNS tricks to randomly send users to a different destination. They&amp;rsquo;ll only know what type of framework they are seeing by a &amp;ldquo;bug&amp;rdquo; in the footer. Sounds neat, right?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>random_jy --help</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 19:54:58 EST</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;person:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Person&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s up! Who am I? Why am I subjecting you to my random thoughts? Because we&amp;rsquo;re on the Internet, and I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off I&amp;rsquo;m married with 1 kid already and another on the way. My family is pretty awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe in doing as much as I can myself, so I like to build or improve things around our house. Plus, nothing will make you appreciate just how lucky you are more than doing manual labor. I dug dirt in the summers before college, it definitely motivated me to become an Engineer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In college I studied Computer Engineering &amp;amp; Software Engineering. After I worked in Embedded Systems, mostly coding up DSP type stuff in C. Although there were some deviations, including Java and Ada. Yes, Ada, and I liked it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now a days I work at &lt;a href=&#34;https//dyn.com&#34;&gt;Dyn&lt;/a&gt; working with Chef, Python, and Varnish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m always looking to learn new things and improve on what I already know. This blog will hopefully capture that never ending journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to contact me, &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/random_jyoung&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://linkedin.com/in/jonryoung/&#34;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; would be best, Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;tech:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Tech&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;powered by &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; (and isn&amp;rsquo;t it awesome?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Base theme is &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/zyro/hyde-x&#34;&gt;Hyde-X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Further theme inspriation from &lt;a href=&#34;http://npf.io/&#34;&gt;npf.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>